Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Good for a snack.
Snacks thanks to your mother
Thanks to your mother
Because of you
I still can't believe it
Nervous, excited and anxious
I'm nervous, excited, anxious...
I'm more excited than I've ever been in my life.
I'm so surprised that I'm here right now
I'm trying to live my life with no regrets.
I'm here now.
God gave me this.
I think it's a miracle.
I want people to think of me as a friend
I want to be able to blow a new wind
I want all the people in Japan to recognize me
I want to be an idol who can bring hope and smiles
I want to be an idol who can bring hope and smiles to people all over Japan.
Since we have been labeled as an official rival of Nogizaka-san, my goal is to become a group that is on par with Nogizaka-san.
My goal is to become a group that can stand up to Nogizaka's group.
Thank you very much for your support.
Hello to all of you who are watching our YouTube Live and other live broadcasts!
I'm Marina Tsuji, your hostess.
Today, I'm Marina Tsuji, and I'll be presenting the announcement of the members of Mugizaka46's official rivals.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We will be live streaming the event from offstage on TikTok and Instagram. Please check them out as well.
Now, without further ado, I would like to introduce the members of Nogizaka46 Official Rivals one by one.
These members were chosen from 35,678 applicants.
Let me introduce them to you now.
Yuho Aoki
I am 20 years old and from Okinawa, Japan.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Smaller Mystery Girl
Love and friendship
I'll be back tomorrow with Kokoro no Girl.
I'm Hitomi Hasegawa, 20 years old, from Saitama, Japan. Please give me your best regards.
Thank you for watching.
I am Hagiwara State, 16 years old, from Shizuoka, Japan. Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
I'm Yamaguchi Wan, 18 years old, from Hyogo, Japan. Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching.
I am Mana Mochinaga, 19 years old, from Tokyo, Japan. Thank you for watching.
I am Master Eye from Tokyo, Japan. Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching.
I am a master eye from Tokyo, Japan.even at the time of
even at the time of ...
Is it?
I am Riko Iwamoto, 15 years old, from Tokyo, Japan. Pleased to meet you.
Thank you for watching.
I'm Aya Nishimori, 19 years old, from Kochi, Japan.
Next notice
I'm Yuji Ito, 21 years old, from Chiba.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Kana de Amida
I'm Ami Kanazawa, 16 years old, from Kanagawa, Japan. Please subscribe to my channel!
Subscribe to our channel!
Thank you for watching!
I am Miisa Yaegashi, 13 years old, from Miyagi, Japan. Please take care of me.
Yu Kudo, from Hokkaido, Japan, is 13 years old. Please give my best regards to him.
Thank you for watching.
I am Nana Shiogama, 20 years old, from Kagoshima, Japan. Thank you very much for watching.
I am Nana Nakamiya, 18 years old. Nice to meet you.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
I am from Fukui prefecture, Iriya, Miyako city, 18 years old. Thank you very much for watching.
I'm Lian Akita, 15 years old, from Hyogo, Japan. Please give me your best regards.
Thank you for watching.
I am Yuki Imai, 17 years old, from Aichi, Japan. Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching!
I am Megumi Sugiura, 14 years old, from Aichi, Japan. Thank you very much for watching.
I am Suzuki Hayaseki, 18 years old, from Tokyo, Japan. Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching.
I am from Tokyo, Yagi and I am 16 years old. Thank you very much for watching.
I am Karen Yanagibori from Tokyo, 17 years old.
Thank you for watching.
I am from Ishikawa, Yoshimoto Kokoner, 17 years old. Thank you for watching.
I am Aoi Anno, 16 years old, from Saitama, Japan. Thank you for watching.
These 23 members were selected from 35,678 applicants.
They are the official rivals of Nogizaka46!
We look forward to working with you all!
Now, for those of you with still cameras, please refrain from using flash photography from this point on.
Please refrain from shooting with flash from this point on.
Now then, I would like to move on to the announcement of the name of the group that you are all anxious about.
What is the name of the group?
Nogizaka46 Official Rivals Group name is here!
The name of the group is "Boku ga mitakatta aozora" ("The blue sky I wanted to see").
What do you think?
I don't know if it's contrary to my expectations or not.
But once again, the management staff has sent us their thoughts on the name of the group.
I will read it out.
Everyone has a dream that they had when they were little.
It is the wish we had for what we want to be when we grow up.
Eventually, as we grow up and realize the gap between our ideals and reality
We stop talking about our dreams.
When did we learn to give up?
It is true that our dreams are far away
There may be many obstacles in the way until we grasp them
But our dreams are always ahead of us.
Beyond the clouds, there is a blue sky
They are about to make their debut
Believe in the blue sky in the darkness before the dawn
Though we who have grown up have given up before we know it
But I want them to see it
The blue sky I've always wanted to see
Please give them your support.
Now that we've announced the name of the group...
Mr. Yanagibori, how about Mr. Yoshimoto?
I thought it would have a number, but I'm happy if you call us "Boku Ao" for short, the blue sky I wish I could have seen.
So far we have had our first training camp, our first music video shooting, and our first shooting for Sazuna, but we haven't seen the blue sky yet because of the continuous rain and unseasonal typhoons.
I hope that we will be able to see blue skies that live up to the name of this group, and grow as a group that lives up to its name.
I hope we can grow as a group that lives up to our name.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much for your support.
Now then, I would like to make an announcement regarding the debut of Aozora, which I have been eagerly awaiting.
The CD debut date will be
August 30, 2023!
The title of our debut song is "Thinking about Blue Sky".
The song was written by Yasushi Akimoto, who also wrote the lyrics for the group's name.
And the center of the group's debut song will be played by
Yagitoa. How do you feel about your first center role?
I am feeling some pressure.
But I feel that this group is a team of 23 members.
I hope we can all work together and do our best.
As Towa-chan said earlier, because we are one group with 23 members
I would like to make the strongest teamwork to support Towa-chan.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Now, the reservation of this debut single "Think about the blue sky" will start from 18:00 today!Now, pre-orders for this debut single "Thinking about Blue Sky" will start at 18:00 today!
We are also planning to hold a debut event and online talk session for CD purchasers! Please check out our official website for more details.
Now, I'm sure that you are already in a state of excitement since your debut comes only 3 months after you passed the audition.
It's all new to me, so I'm anxious every day.
But we are all working very hard.
I'm really enjoying every scene.
It's like we're living a new adolescence as a group of 23.
I'd be very happy if you could watch over us with us.
I'm also really looking forward to talking to everyone in Japan at the events.
I hope to meet a lot of fans in the future.
In addition, a part of our debut song "Thinking about the Blue Sky" will be available on TikTok from 6pm today.
A part of the song "Think about the blue sky" will be streamed on TikTok from 6pm today!
We hope you will be able to listen to it before anyone else at this event.
Let's listen to it here and now!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much for watching!
Surrounded by others, I was aiming for...
I lost sight of the sun.
I forgot who I was.
You were the one who reminded me of you.
How many times I've crossed over to the other side.
I know...
Thank you very much.
You all seemed to be enjoying the song, but how do you feel after listening to this debut song again?
Yes, my name is Akira.
I remember how I felt when I heard this song for the first time at the camp.
How about you, Aya?
Yes, I am Nishimori.
I really feel that until a while ago, we were all just ordinary girls going about our daily lives,
I can't believe I'm here, and I still feel like I'm dreaming.
But with these 23 of us, we want to give you dreams and hopes.
I want to give you hope.
Please look forward to the release of the full song.
Okay, Leanne, before that, go ahead.
Now, before that, Lianne, please go ahead.
Akita.
Listening to the debut song once again, I feel that we are getting closer to completion.
The lyrics of this song have many parts that I can really relate to, so I think a lot of people will enjoy it.
Yes, that's right. There are many parts of this song that I can really relate to, so I hope everyone will pay attention to them and enjoy the song.
Next, Riko-chan, who is far away, please come in.
I'm Iwamoto.
During the dance lesson, the sound of our singing voice suddenly started to play without any forward motion,
I was so moved that I almost burst into tears,
I was so moved that I almost burst into tears, but I danced as hard as I could.
I heard that Muira and Ellen were crying a lot.
Everyone was singing while holding back tears.
Lastly, Nana, what do you think?
Yes, I am Shirakama.
I finally feel like I am one step closer to being an idol,
I am not satisfied with my current position, but I would like to be a person who can give someone courage and hope, even if only a little.
No, I will!
Yay!
Thank you for your powerful words.
Now, in conjunction with the pre-distribution of the video, the TikTok Effect
Boku Sei Challenge will also be distributed,
We hope you will use our debut song to make a TikTok post.
Released on August 30.
Think about Blue Sky. We look forward to working with you.
Please give me your best regards.
Thank you very much.
Now, the members of Kyokusei, who have just made their debut today, will tell us about their appealing points.
Each of you has written them down on a flip chart, so please prepare yourselves.
I'm sure you are wondering what kind of appeal points you have.
Now, did I win the flip cards?
Now, let's have a round of "Se-o-no-Open!
Se-no, open!
Oh, there are a lot of things to talk about,
Let's start with you, Mr. Kudo.
Let's start with you, Mr. Kudo, on the subject of softness,
What do you have to show us?
Well, my appeal point is my softness.
I can turn my legs, but I can't do it now. But I can't do it now.
So, it's a cut, right?
I can do forward bends.
Okay, Mr. Kudo, I'm looking forward to working with you.
Oh, wow!
Your arms touch the floor perfectly.
Did you take any lessons?
I took dance lessons.
That's why you are so soft.
I try my best to stretch and make my body soft.
I hope you will continue to use your softness to dance well.
Yes, I will.
Now, is Akita-san here? Let's go, Akita-san.
You wrote strongly about your spirit and perseverance, but what does this mean?
You look so cute with your twins and all.
I've been doing karate since I was a little girl.
I think I have more spirit and determination than anyone else.
May I show it to you now?
May I?
Please do.Please.
Oh!
Yes!
Amazing!
I can't believe I heard that voice coming from Akita-san!
There's a gap between the two.
You all have various specialties.
Lastly...
Mr. Sunaga, I'm wondering about you...
Mr. Sunaga, a big hello and thank you for today.
Yes, when I enter a site or meet someone who is involved in the project, I always greet them with a loud voice.
I always greet them with a loud voice.
Also, each member writes a diary every day.
I put it in the upper right corner of the page.
I always write "Thank you for today" in the upper right corner of the page.
I always write "Thank you" in the upper right corner.
That's the end.
Thank you for being cute with me!
Can I ask you all to say thank you in that big voice of yours?
Can I ask you all to say thank you for today?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Wow, you must have reached the people in the back.
I wanted to ask you more, but it's time for me to go.
I'd like to take this opportunity to let you all know about the many things we're going to be doing in the future.
Well, thank you very much for your cooperation, but this concludes the announcement of the official rival members of Nogizaka46.
I wish you all the best in the future.
For those of you in the media who were able to join us for the live broadcast, please let us end our coverage here. Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much for joining us today.
Please subscribe to our channel.